{
    "id": "bf93632129ef4ea4a02b20bb2b5711af",
    "title": "By and until | Grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "30d62bfddb6147aa9149262c4433de12",
            "title": "By And Until | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I will keep asking …………………. you send my payment.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The shop is open ...................... 9 pm.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They said that they would finish the job …………………. Friday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I waited for him ……………….. 12 o’clock and then I went home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "by"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be staying in this city ………………… the end of this month.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be home …………………. five o’clock.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. the end of the party, everybody was drunk.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "By",
                        "Until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be in bed ……………….. the time you get home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be ready ………………… the time you arrive.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will wait here …………………. you come back.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "by"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}